Today is the thirty-eighth day.
-two days left to set up my business.
I'm here in an abandoned shed and the bathroom.
He's used to do a cleaning.
And first I'm going to go down there at the gas station,
have some coffee.
Let's go,
let's go.
So, bro,
and then it's okay,
how's it going?
Hey, Juninho,
can you use the bucket there real quick?
I got this bathroom here,
freak.
You are not turning on the smell,
OK,
let's exchange 1 idea.
I live on Chevette,
but it's broken.
The guys let me sleep in an abandoned shed that I'm renting.
And here I am creating these ideas and documenting all of this for you.
Hence the day.
Ask for the chevas mano and it will take a
couple of days to arrive at the free market.
At least it's the right piece.
is on
OMG MY GOD FROM HEAVEN.
I'm fine guys that gave me 1 insight?
Imagine if you can pay attention how many more sales you can't make?
Man,
because you're managing to attract your customer until the end and within that,
you improve your positioning,
attract,
fight and it starts to be more interesting than interested.
It's not you selling,
it's the people buying it.
-two days until I open a business.
Now I'm going to create my ideas and with everything because oh,
doubt holds and certainty pushes away.
Tamo together
haha?